so what made you think you could get away with this little stunt huh I thought if I picked a
movie that wasn't all sparkly and mainstream you guys would be too dumb to figure it out
oh it's fine if you don't get caught looks like the only dumb one here is you missy
that was stupid and so lame
okay fine I'm very sorry so what the crap are we supposed to do about this about what we don't
have a film anymore unless you think there's a way we can still use the stolen script we're not
making money off it and Rika doubts anyone would know you've got to be kidding me don't you know
who I think I am I can't be in some knockoff movie we're trashing Yozara's fake script if I'm going
to star in a film it has to be an original yeah but there's no time to write a whole new script
that's the problem I'm not suggesting we write a new one ta-da uh I can't see it what I hold in my
delicate silky royal hand is an original script I wrote it on the sly in case Yozara predictably
let us all down of course you did oh wow what an awesome title Senna all that and she's a writer
too sing your songs of gratitude quickly my minions we've got work to do how does it feel Yozara losing
such a great job to me this is the closest I've ever come to meeting a real-life criminal hope you
enjoyed your five minutes of fame we'll gladly pick up the remaining ten and spend it wisely
that's a perfect look for what I'm trying to do I hope you can act
uh
you
Oh, look, it's a witch.
So cool.
No self-respecting witch would dress like this.
Are you listening to me, meat-breath?
Below.
So it's boys over the what?
The slope.
That's correct.
Okay, everyone, let's take it from the fight scene.
Fine.
And no matter what they tell me, there's no going back now, now.
Ah, no!
What is this power?
I'll get you.
Goodness, you're pretty good at this acting thing.
That's perfect!
Now this is where you jumper!
And cut!
Crossfade to next morning!
What's a crossfade?
Yosara, this is where you self-destruct.
How am I supposed to do that?
Oh, please, I don't know any actresses who can't blow themselves up.
Don't worry, Rika will cover that in post with some CG.
I'll do everything I can to make sure our friendship outlasted planet Earth.
Now, let us give thanks for the mercy we have been given.
We give thanks to the all-knowing, all-powerful goddess, Sweena.
Yes, indeed.
She is but love inside me.
I said she's but love.
High school friendships, singing, magic, superpowers, intergalactic samurai robot wars on top of Gai Gai love scenes.
How do you put all that in a script and have it make sense?
Can you make sure there's a glitter trail?
Oh, well, whatever.
I guess we can always say we're making an indie film.
Rika's very sorry for bothering you like this.
She knows you're busy.
Hey, don't sweat it.
I just realized.
Maybe I shouldn't be walking alone with Rika.
You know, Rika just realized we're walking alone together down the hallway.
It's sort of a first step, isn't it?
A first step for what?
I shouldn't have to tell you.
Hey, what was that noise for?
And here we are.
Welcome.
I haven't been in this room since we first met.
It still smells the same.
I don't even remember how long ago that was.
It was 122 days, 8 hours, and 37 minutes ago.
Have you been counting this whole time?
No counting.
Rika just remembers.
Now, if we broke it down by seconds, that would require actual counting, and Rika does not have time for that.
Oh.
Sect Sigma?
Tell no one if you want to live.
Whoa.
Rika used to have a fingerprint and voice recognition code on the lock to make it even more like a secret hideaway.
That's intense, Rika.
You're more into this nerdy stuff than I thought.
Do you also cosplay while you're in here?
Rika can tell when someone is making fun of her joy.
Whoa.
This is unbelievable.
You can go ahead and set that equipment back down anywhere you like.
Cool.
This is crazy.
You're the first person Rika has ever even let into this room.
Huh.
She pours her heart out, and all you've got for Rika is a lousy huh?
Aren't you moved?
A girl is inviting you into her room alone for the first time ever.
Just because you live in it doesn't mean this place qualifies as a girl's room.
All right.
Well, I hope all the equipment works out.
Let me know how it goes.
Oh, wait.
Don't go.
Hmm?
Rika wants your thoughts on the special effects she added to the scenes we shot yesterday.
And don't matter what you tell me, there's no going back now.
Now!
Ah!
What is this power?
I'll get you.
You're more powerful than I thought you were.
Whoa.
You've done an awesome job.
Oh, Rika couldn't wait to show you.
She's glad you like it.
I love it.
It looks like an entirely different movie.
How long did it take you?
Hmm.
A long time, but the result was worth it.
Yeah, totally.
I feel bad you're doing so much on your own.
Do you need help?
Not at all.
It does take a while, but Rika's not stressed out about it.
Huh?
Rika has worked on fanfic movies and some games before, but only by herself.
There's a little pressure this time since she's doing this for people she knows.
Especially since one of those people is you.
Uh.
Okay.
What's the neighbor's club binder?
Oh.
Here, Rika will show you.
Don't freak out, but Rika took some secret photos.
I was changing, you perv!
Yes, but it isn't what you think.
Then please, start explaining.
Rika needed them for reference.
Remember that time we all played the Romancing Saga game together?
Yeah.
Rika wanted to make everyone's CG players as accurate as possible, so she used actual photos.
Uh.
No way.
All that work just to create a video game character?
I'm impressed.
There you go.
Now you know everything.
Promise, Rika, you won't judge her, okay?
I won't, but...
But what?
You hate it, don't you?
Huh?
No.
I was just thinking I should go.
Talk to you later.
Oh.
Okay, yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Oh.
That's too bad.
Rika had a really great time.
It was the first time Rika ever played a game with other people.
That's the most fun she's ever had.
She always has the best attitude, no matter what.
Out of all the Neighbors Club members, seems making friends is most important to her.
At least she seems to be trying the hardest.
Kids, this way.
Parents, wait there.
Here, take one.
Tell all your friends about us.
Whoa!
Wow!
That's a big bear!
Hey, big brother, is it okay if we get crates?
Uh, sure, but maybe later.
Yay!
Best day ever!
Thanks for bringing me.
You're acting like you've never been to a festival before.
I had no idea these kinds of things even happen.
Back when I was going to school, all we ever did was work and study.
It took me three minutes to find it.
We need to hurry.
Where's the AV room?
I'm supposed to know this how?
Maybe because you went to this school two years ago?
Huh?
Sorry to disappoint you, but that wasn't me.
Are you sure about that?
Yep.
I went to a public school a few blocks away from me.
That's right.
I remember now.
You had to take the entrance exam, didn't you?
There's no way you were grandfathered in.
Thanks for the biography, Yozara.
Let's go.
The AV room isn't going to come looking for us.
Please, take your seats.
Class two second year will now present an original film.
We ask that you remain silent during the screening and turn off or silence all cell phones.
Lucky for us, they're running behind.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Class two hopes you enjoy their shorts starring Lady Coboteau.
It's Lady Coboteau now?
She used her real name?
It's like a reverse Cinderella with dragons.
Our movie just got its butt kicked.
Bravo, Coboteau, two huge thumbs up!
That was beautiful.
Talent runs in the family.
You must be so proud of her.
Rika's more of an action-adventure type, but she can hang with a good romantic drama now and then.
Me too.
It actually gave me ideas for things we could do with our move.
What now, Senna?
I can't get over how cute she is.
She's like a teeny tiny doll that you can squish in your arms.
Coboteau is the greatest actress I've ever seen in my life.
And she's so hot.
Oh, I know. The entire audience was like melting in her hands.
And can we talk about how our first showing was almost overflowing?
If people keep talking about it, we're not going to have enough seats.
We should totally sell tickets.
People would buy them just to see Coboteau.
There she is, our precious little starlass!
It's been such a long time since I've seen you or smelled you!
I've missed you punches and punches, my little angel mouselet!
You're so cute, I need a princess with!
And you smell so amazing!
Get off me! I can't breathe!
What are you guys even doing here?
Kotika, you jerk! I told you not to come!
Um, hi! Are you Coboteau's brother? I've heard so much about you.
Oh, yeah.
What did you think? Wasn't Coboteau just unbelievable?
Yeah, everybody was. In fact, the whole movie was amazing.
Hey, Coboteau! Did you hear? Your haughty big brother thought you were amazing!
I totally agree, Coboteau. You blew my mind! I thought you were the best thing about it!
Uh, sorry. It looks like our diva just needed a moment.
No worries.
So, uh, is Coboteau popular here or something? I'm a little freaked out right now.
Yeah! Duh! And it's more than just our class.
The whole school worship's room wants to be your friend.
I had no idea.
Except...
Hmm?
Well, I don't know if that actually makes her popular since she doesn't want to talk to anybody.
I kinda don't think she likes people very much.
Okay, I shouldn't say people, I guess. Just not us.
Hmm. Very interesting.
We're always telling her how much we adore her, but it's like the more we try to get close to her,
the more she pulls away or maybe she just doesn't take us seriously.
Oh my gosh, please don't hate my guts. I'm not trying to badmouth your sister. I love her.
I'm really a fan of her awkwardness. It's like totes endearing.
See you later.
Doesn't take compliments. Pulls away when you try to get close.
Sure sounds like that runs in the family.
Huh? Sorry, what did you say?
What's wrong, Maria?
I'm bored. I wanna go home and stuff my face.
Huh?
Coo-coo-coo.
Dry your mortal eyes. You shall wait for me no longer.
Ah! The smelly vampire has returned and we can kill her once and for all!
Do we stone her? Drown her? How are we gonna do it?
Your idiocy amuses me to no end, minion of God. Someday you will look great.
Ah!
Oh, why do you keep jumping at me like that? Are you trying to get me to destroy you?
Are you trying to get me to destroy you? I can smell the crazy leafy out of you.
I have powers that would have your God on his knees begging me for lessons.
Okay, let's get moving. We can film Kobito's scene next since she's already warmed up.
I didn't even know Kobito was in this.
Yeah, of course she is. I realize this might make it a little awkward for you because we've decided to have her do all your secrets.
Is she replacing me or was I just a stand-in for her all along?
Look at that sunset. It's the perfect location for our next shot. Let's go!
We're on it. You can count on us.
It's no use, you tragic excuse for a nun. I'll crush you with the same powers that bewitch my audience.
Poopy vampire, you think your performance is so great, you're in for a surprise!
Kobito, wait! You can play when we're done!
Kodaka, let's move. We're burning daylight.
Okay, okay. I'm coming.
Good afternoon. Look what the sun shined, Dragon.
Great day for a sports festival, don't you think?
You've all worked so hard.
I hope you're as proud of yourselves as I am of the entire student body.
I'm excited to see the results of all your efforts and talents.
Nice.
Parents, we are so happy to have you today.
So our student body president is a girl.
As always, thank you for your continued support for your children and our institution.
This event represents...
What now? I don't have anything to do until they're ready for me.
Hey.
Are you bored too?
Yeah, I'm probably just gonna head home soon.
Whoa, what? Why?
Ugh, it's not a big deal. I should have just skipped.
It's early and somebody already pissed me off.
Who would that be?
That skinny ponytail who spoke at the opening ceremony.
No way. I had no idea you even knew the student body president.
Well, we've never actually spoken. But I know enough to know that I hate her.
Huh?
Hinata Hideaka. She's a third year, and this is her second term as student body president,
so that should tell you how ridiculously popular she is.
She's smart and good at every sport imaginable. All the teams ask her to fill in for them.
Even though she's busy, she'll make time for anything.
But you're two minutes, and you are there for a reason?
I mean, I am so I am and I am so happy.
And what?
You know, what are you going to do?
I'm very close.
What are you going to do now?
How are you going to do now?
I'm going to try not to do now.
You are going to do now.
fill in for them. Even though she's busy, she will make time for anyone who asks for a favor.
Of course all the freshmen think she's like some kind of goddess. Yeah, why would anyone like
someone like her? Well, it's not just that. It's because she's so not fake about it. I mean,
Meet McNasty does all those sorts of things, but she does it to get people to worship her. She
doesn't actually like anyone, you know? But Hinata is kind of like King Lear in a way.
And what does that mean? It's a Shakespeare play, idiot. It's one of his most famous tragedies
about an old evil king who causes his country nothing but misery until his own horrific death.
Pretty much the entire cast dies in his wake. Uh, that's kind of a creepy comparison. I think
it accurately represents my desire to see her suffer the same amount of pain she's caused me.
She's making me want to puke just talking about her. I need to go to the nurse's office and lie down.
So you're allergic to genuinely nice people. Got it.
Rika? What the hell is she doing up there?
Kodaka? The hell are you doing here?
I was about to ask you the same thing.
Oh, um, Rika likes the feel of the wind.
Well, you'll certainly get a lot of it dressed like that.
Rika was feeling sporty today, so she decided to wear her gym outfit. What do you think?
Yep, that's the right one. Why don't you go down and participate?
Nah, Rika's got a lot of work left to do. Not that she would join in if she didn't.
Holy crap. You stayed up all night working on the movie, didn't you?
Oh, gross. Is it that obvious? Rika was totally going to wear her glasses today, but then she forgot.
Something tells me I still would have known. Anyway, I hope you realize we appreciate you.
Stop! Stop giving Rika genuine heartfelt compliments without notice!
Her mind can't take it, and she's about to explode!
Sorry, I take it back.
Oh, yay! The race is about to start. Here they go!
Look! Senna's already got a head start!
Crap or duck! How does she run with those things?
I don't know, but you seem pretty mad about it.
No, Rika's just impressed with everything she can do on top of looking that way.
Yep, she has a gift.
What are your thoughts? Go ahead. Rika wants to know all the dirty details.
There are no dirty details. She's just another club member, silly.
She's also your betrothed.
That's crazy, and it's not even happening anymore.
Rika thinks that you might want to update Senna on that situation.
Huh? Wait, what do you mean?
Rika doesn't understand how you can complain that you're lonely
when you don't let anyone get close to you.
You pretend not to notice when someone is interested in your life.
Then you make jokes so that no one will know when you're upset.
Even though no one's given good reason,
you convince yourself no one likes you so you never get hurt.
I get it. Is this what you want to tell Kobito?
If so, go for it. It sounds good.
That's not gonna work.
Rika knows that you know the truth, but...
She will continue to play the role you want her to play
and protect your secrets so you're comfortable.
But for how long, Kodaka?
Rika predicts these games will get old after a little while.
What about...
Shut up, Rika!
Rika!
I gotta go. Talk to you later.
Kodaka, please always remember.
Rika would bend over backwards for you anytime, anywhere.
Huh? Sorry, I missed a lot of that.
She would bend over backwards to help me anytime I needed it.
The wind may have swallowed her words,
but I've known the truth about how Rika feels for a very long time.
So...
You
You played dumb, but my heart knew the truth all along.
What? What?
You denied when Rika cried, but she saw right through you. Yeah!
You're not exactly singing the same song as Rika, are you?
I'm sorry. I'll stop and try to collaborate and listen this time.
What? What?
Next time, dismay of I the chicken.
Kodaka, will you marry Rika?
No love games, turn our bad romance around!
Um, no.
Not even for the song?
No love games, turn our bad romance around!